Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Addendum
  - Family events, history, residences
    - Allie May Autry Kelley estate (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Family history (Box 100, Folder 9-11)